dfkangxin.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy Policy

dfkangxin Communications considers your privacy to be very important. We follow the privacy principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement, and are registered with the U.S. Department of Commerce's safe harbor program. 

This privacy policy covers information we collect and how we use it, choices that you have for your personal information and sharing and transferring of information. 

##  Information We Collect: 

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as searches of our advertisers database and accessing information, forums and articles on the Websites.  For other services, such as posting to the forums or the free classified and for setting up an advertising account, we may collect the following types of information: 

  * Member Information - When you become a Member of us, we ask you for personal information such as your name, email address, your firms address, a user ID and an account password. We may provide Member Information to companies or individuals who may wish to contact you to offer their goods or services. 

  * Personal Information - Personal Information includes Member Information.  In addition, for our advertising programs, we also require credit card or other payment account information.  We maintain credit card and other payment account information in encrypted form on secure servers. We do not provide credit card information, your user ID or any password to anyone outside of dfkangxin Communications. 

  * Cookies - When you visit one of our Websites we send one or more Cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences.  Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you do, however, some features and services may not function properly. 

  * Server logs - When you visit one of our Websites our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These Server Logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your visit and the identity of any cookies that were sent to your browser. 

  * User communications - When you send email or other communication to dfkangxin Communications, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

  * Newsletter requests - When you join one of our mailing lists you provide us with Personal Information such as your name and email address.  We use this information to deliver newsletters to you. 

  * Affiliated sites - We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to dfkangxin Communications in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

  * Links - dfkangxin Communications may gather information about which links have been followed on our Websites. For more information about links, URLs and information embedded in Links, please see our Definitions. 

  * Other sites - This privacy policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by dfkangxin Communications. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

##  How We Use Information We Collect: 

dfkangxin Communications only processes personal information for the purposes described in this privacy policy. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising. 

  * Auditing and conducting research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services. 

  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our Websites, and Developing new services. 

dfkangxin Communications processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. We may process personal information to deliver the services that we provide and, in some cases, we may process Personal Information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners. 

##  Choices For Personal Information: 

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than stated in this Privacy Policy or for the purpose for which it was collected, we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this privacy policy we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use Sensitive Personal Information, unless you have voluntarily posted such information, which we do not recommend. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services. In that case, however, dfkangxin Communications may not be able to provide those services to you. 

##  Information Sharing: 

dfkangxin Communications only shares Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of dfkangxin Communications in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We may provide Member Information, such as your email address, to companies or individuals who may wish to contact you to offer their goods or services.  We do not provide credit card information, your user ID or any password to anyone outside of dfkangxin Communications. 

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 

  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing Personal Information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this privacy policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation or Valid Legal Process (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof,  detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of dfkangxin Communications, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If dfkangxin Communications becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of Aggregated, Non-personal Information, such as the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisers link or searched for a particular term, for example.  Such information does not identify you individually. 

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year.  If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. 

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data. 

##  Information Security: 

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to Personal Information to dfkangxin Communications employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

##  Data Integrity: 

dfkangxin Communications processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this privacy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

##  Accessing And Updating Personal Information: 

When you use dfkangxin Communications services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information that they want to access, correct or remove before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that we cannot authenticate, would jeopardize the privacy of others, would require us to access information that is not readily accessible or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.
